And your brain is the most powerful weapon.
I talk about that in one of these chapters.
Your brain is the most powerful weapon in the world.
Once you put away your phones and your computers
and all that shit we have nowadays, that's great.
We're up to date.
You know, but your brain is the only thing you have
when you're going through depression,
when you're going through hard times,
you're going through death, real life shit.
You can't Google that shit, man.
You're alone.
You may have a shrink.
You're going to.
You may have a best thing you're going to.
But there's 24 hours in the day where you're alone
in this brain.
And your brain is talking to you in all kinds of ways.
And at once the control you're pulling these different pockets.
If you can't control your own brain
and your brain controls you, the fuck.
You got to tell your brain where you want to go
and how you want to go and how you can get there.
You got to control it.
If not, it's cool.